Saving the world, one enemy at a time.
Ultimate Avengers: The Movie is a action, animation,
family film directed by Curt Geda.
When a nuclear missile was fired at Washington in 1945, Captain
America managed to detonate it in the upper atmosphere.
But then he fell miles into the icy depths of the North
Atlantic, where he remained lost for over sixty years.
But now, with the world facing the very same evil, Captain
America must rise again as our last hope for survival.
Steve Rogers / Captain America (voice), played by Justin Gross.
Janet Pym / The Wasp (voice), played by Grey DeLisle.
Hank Pym / Giant Man (voice), played by Nolan North.
Natalia Romanoff / Black Widow (voice), played by Olivia D'Abo.
Tony Stark / Iron Man (voice), played by Marc Worden.
Bruce Banner (voice), played by Michael Massee.
Ultimate Avengers: The Movie (also known simply as Ultimate Avengers) is a 2006 American
animated superhero film based on the Ultimates comic book series by Marvel Comics.
The film is the first installment in the Marvel Animated Features (MAF) film series, and follows
Captain America, who is de-thawed and recruited by Nick Fury to fight an alien race.
Premiering on February 7, 2006, at WonderCon, Ultimate Avengers was
released direct-to-video in the United States on February 21.
A sequel to the film, titled Ultimate Avengers 2: Rise of the Panther, premiered at San-Diego
Comic Con on July 22, 2006, five months after the first film was released.
The film explores themes of mask, superhero, alien
life-form, based on comic, alien.
The tone is thought_provoking.